Guide to the Yale University Building Assignment Plans
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University building assignment plans
1924-1976
RU 4
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of assignment plans showing, by floor, the complete layout of various Yale buildings at the time the drawings were rendered.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by region/chronology (building) code.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of assignment plans showing, by floor, the complete layout of various Yale buildings at the time the drawings were rendered.
College buildings; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records; Floor plans (orthographic projections); Yale University -- Buildings
- Assignment plans for Yale University buildings, 1924-1976; Series I
  - 1:02 Connecticut Hall, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1:20 Street Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1:23 Farnam Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1:24 Durfee Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4a)
  - 1:25 Battell Chapel, undated (Box 1, Folder 4b)
  - 1:28 Dwight Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1:29 Lawrance Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1:30 Chittenden Hall (Box 1)
    General note
    see 1:39 Linsly-Chittenden Hall
  - 1:32 Welch Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1:33 Vanderbilt Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1:35 Phelps Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1:39 Linsly-Chittenden Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1:40 Wright Hall, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1:43 Edwin McClellan Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2:11 305 Crown St., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2:22 161-163 York St., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2:31 26 High St., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 3:07 University Theatre, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 3:09 294-296 Elm St., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 3:25 Davenport and Pierson Colleges, [1970?] (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 3:31 215 Park St., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 3:32 204 York St., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 3:33 205 Park St, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 3:36 University News Bureau, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 3:37 217 Park St, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 3:42 211 Park St, [1973?] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 3:43 Art and Architecture Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 3:49 1195 Chapel St., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 3:60 212 York St., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 4:03 Peabody Museum, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 4:04 Sloan Physics Laboratory, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 4:22 232 York St., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 4:28 Bradford and Saybrook Colleges, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 4:34 Jonathan Edwards College, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 4:37 Art Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 5:10 Hall of Graduate Studies, 1970, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 5:16-17 Morse and Ezra Stiles Colleges, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 6:00 78 Lake Place, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 6:05 20 Ashmun St., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 6:16 Payne Whitney Gymnasium, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 6:17 Ray Tompkins House, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 6:28 50 Ashmun St., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 7:31 Sterling Memorial Library, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 7:36 Trumbull College, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 8:16 Sterling Law School, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 9:24 Sprague Memorial Hall, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 9:33 Harkness Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 9:34 Calhoun College, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 9:35 Berkeley College, 1971, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 9:36 Cross Campus Library, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings, 1970, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 10:18 Woodbridge Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 10:25 Beinecke Rare Books Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 11:03 Hendrie Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 11:07 74, 76, 78, Wall St., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 11:09 Yale University Press, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 11:09 143 Elm St, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 11:11 Faculty Club, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 11:13 320 Temple St., undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 11:17 435 College St., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 11:19 Stoeckel Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 11:20 451 College St., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 11:23 302 Temple St, [1973?] (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 12:28 Silliman College, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 12:29 St. Anthony Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 12:29 493 College St., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 13:06 51 Prospect St., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 13:07 Kirtland Hall, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 13:08 Leet Oliver Memorial Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 13:09 Dunham Laboratory, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - 13:16 Strathcona Hall (SSS), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - 13:17 24 Hillhouse Ave., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - 13:18 Becton Engineering and Applied Science Building, no date, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 14:04 Mason Laboratory, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - 14:06 442 Temple St., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - 14:07 432-434 Temple St., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - 14:09 15 Hillhouse Ave., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - 14:11 One Hillhouse Ave., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - 14:15 370 Temple St., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - 14:21 Helen Hadley Hall, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - 14:22 109-111 Grove St., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - 14:25 Yale University Health Services, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - 14:29 405 Temple St., undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - 14:31 88 Temple St., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - 15:02 Hammond Hall, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - 15:05 Brewster Hall, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - 15:08 70 Sachem St., undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - 15:09 Urban Hall, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - 15:10 Williams Hall, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - 16:01 56 Hillhouse Ave., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - 16:02 28 Hillhouse Ave., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - 16:04 52 Hillhouse Ave., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - 16:05 77 Prospect St, [1924?] (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - 16:06 89 Trumbull St., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - 16:08 111 Prospect St., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - 16:09 30 Hillhouse Ave., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - 16:10 135 Prospect St., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - 17:05 158 Whitney Ave., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - 17:06 51 Hillhouse Ave., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - 17:09 43 Hillhouse Ave., undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - 17:10 27 Hillhouse Ave., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - 17:11 35 Hillhouse Ave (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - 18:04 155 Whitney Ave., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - 18:05 175 Whitney Ave., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - 19:01 276 Prospect St., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - 19:02 360 Prospect St., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - 19:16 230 Prospect St., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - 19:17 Ingall's Rink, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - 19:19 Greeley Memorial Laboratory, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - 19:20 254 Prospect St., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - 20:00 216 Prospect St., undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - 20:02 Osborn Memorial Laboratory, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - 20:05 Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, 1967, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - 20:07 Sage-Bowers Hall, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - 20:08 301 Prospect St., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - 20:09 340 Edwards St., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - 20:13 Nuclear Structures Laboratory, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - 20:13 Accelerator Laboratories, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - 20:14 Gibbs Research Laboratory, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - 20:15 Oceanographic and Ornithological Laboratories, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - 20:16 334 Edwards St., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - 20:18 285 Prospect St., undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - 20:19 Kline Geology Laboratory, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - 20:20 Kline Addition to the Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - 20:23 Kline Biology Laboratory, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - 20:24 354 Edwards St., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 125a)
  - 21 386 Prospect St., undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - 21:6 Divinity School, no date, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - 22 Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1971, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - 22 Yale Medical Group, undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - 22:22 Jane Ellen Hope Memorial Building, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - 22:67 Farnam Memorial Building, Brady Memorial Laboratories, Lauder Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - 22:162 Harkness Memorial Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - 22:167 Laboratories of Epidemiology and Public Health, undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - 22:168 Laboratory of Clinical Investigation, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - 23:03 Yale Observatory (Bethany), 1961 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - 25:2 Yale Bowl, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - 25:3 Yale Armory, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - 25:5 Lapham Field House, [1972, 1973?] (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - 26:3 Gales Ferry Boathouse, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - 26:5 Bob Cook Boathouse, undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Married Student Housing, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Madison Square Garden Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 142)